Let us start our discussion with the any disk silent installation.
Many times in incidents, the ransomware or some other incidents, the threat type was silently
installing the any disk without clicking next next.
So this is a pretty simple way of a threat type to us.
If they didn't get command and control, if they didn't get an RDP against the machine.
So this technique is one of important things because a lot of EDRs will not capture
this any disk silent installation.
So to install the any disk silently, you need to have a any disk in your server.
You can download it in your server and you can upload the files to, you can upload the
file to the target directory.
Let me push this any disk into the Apache folder and I will start the Apache in my
column machine, so we know how to utilize the login and deliver the file into the target
machine.
We will get dash F, STTP 192 168 18.49 slash and 14 slash any disk dot exe.
We can put, can put this into the C slash user slash public slash any disk or PX.
Let's wait for some second.
Yeah, right, okay, my Windows machine was suddenly terminator, so that's the problem.
Yes, I was thinking why it was taking a lot of time, so here is the problem.
So Windows machine was terminated and it was turning on again.
Let me pause this video and resume on my Windows machine was ready.
So now you can see the third tutorial uploaded the any disk file into the machine.
So now you are in the system 32 directory, we need to move it, we need to move to the
CDC slash the slash public, let's give DIR, now we can see any disk that was successfully
installed on our machine.
So let's try the unit is installation, so this is the command to any disk install the
any disk silently on the machine, so now it's command get executed, let's see our Windows
machine how this looks like, so now you can see any disk, any disk is installed on the
machine, so here you can see the any disk was present on the machine, so any disk will be
installed on the directory, the program file 686, here you can find the any disk that has
been installed, the next part we need to sit some some password for any disk, okay.
Let me sit a password here, any us, so we know the any disk was present on the directory
program 886, okay, usually the end address will be installed on the directory only, okay,
so let me, how the password has been said let's see the difference of what happened
on the any disk, let's move on to program data and we can see any disk, so here we have
a, you, you can see a lot of files, a lot of files that was present on the machine, right,
the end address creates, so we service.com, so I didn't used any, I didn't download it
from Google or I didn't click the can install data in the machine, but it was automatically
installed on the machine, right, so if I open the any disk, so the any disk will be
installed, okay, so we can, we can trigger the any disk in our calling machine from our
calling machine, so that was, that was IEC, you know, EC1, before executing the any disk,
so if you see the nature of an any disk, so the any disk will show some ID, you, this
is an ID of an any disk, so let me go to the Windows machine and the edge, tell you how
any disk will be working, you need to know the ID one nine five seven five eight two
zero one five one nine five seven five eight two zero seven five this is the ID of any
disk and it was asking for a password, so what we have said and it was, it was asking
some permissions, right, so once the permission has been given, I can see the Windows machine,
okay, I can, I even I can control the Windows machine again, some, it's look like similar
to an RDP, right, I can control the any disk from this machine, so I can, I can go
to Google, I can download any ransomware sample and I can install, this is a coolest feature
of any disk, see how the Windows system, a actor, so let's cancel the any disk from here,
let's Google this and now it was blank, so let's open the any disk from our Kali environment,
we are silently installing right, but we do not have a, let's think about we do not have
an interaction from the Windows machine, we do not have any interaction, any interaction,
GUI interaction, okay, we do not have any GUI interactions in the target machine, we
will only have a command home to work with and command home, let's start the any disk
from Kali machine, now.
let's see, I think, but if it will, it will start
to trigger the any disk from, let's try to trigger the any disk from the public directory,
let's see, usually this is, I don't know, why, this cross not working, let's see, okay,
Let me say a little bit.
Still, it's showing something but usually the inner space dot, if we give this command, let's
see my permission.
If it will take some time, it will be necessary, the permission is command from that
check.
It will be a new disk, it's triggering our content.
So, if you see if I execute this command, a disk will be automatically get triggered.
But, it was not triggering from, from, so, yeah, now, now it worked, now it worked, okay.
Now, it triggered, I can see the interface, so, let's think, we do not have any interactions,
so we need to, we need this address to get, to connect with the any disk.
Usually, the any disk will be, files will be present on the directory, the program data
plus any, let's see if we can see any disk, so here you can find a few files, like
ads, bc, dash, trace, but most of the time, nds will give you an id, executing this command,
nowadays it was not working, I don't know what was the reason behind that, it was not
working and let's take the any disk id from, from this one, system.conf, so here you can
find few informations, ad security update, so ad. any disk, any net.id, so here you can find
the address of one, any disk, right, so once you get the address of the address, we can use
that address and we can connect it from the machine, right, so this will be the easiest
thing, so we got a command and control, so we can control our, control our, any disk from
this machine, right, so this is a nice technique to understand how the threat factors will
be silently installing the any disk and they will be gripping the any disk id, the address
of any disk and they will be connect it to the, from the host, okay, let's hop off from
here and we'll connect you guys in the next video, so we can see what are the other tools,
command and control tools, which we have in mitre test command and control, which we can,
which which threat factors will use for the malicious focus, so any disk will be one
of an important one, so we have achieved our goal, we just uploaded an any disk file, what
we did, let's see, we uploaded an any disk file using sir tutel.exe and then once we
uploaded, we tried to install the any disk in a silent way, silent and we set an any
disk password and we just tried to open any disk and file it was succeeded, so once we
needed a saskin opened, we needed the any disk id to connect, so that we just, we just
see the content of system.config file that was present under the C program data and it is
directory, so it was this and once we got the id, we just that id in our primary machine
any disk, so that was my primary machine, primary machine any disk and we connected that one.
So I hope you have a clear understanding about this video, we'll hop off and we'll connect
you guys in the next video, see you, bye bye.